dizzywood.com 2013-09-01

# Dizzywood | Privacy Policy

### Dizzywood Privacy Policy / California Privacy Rights

#### Effective Date

This Privacy Policy was last updated on February 5, 2010, and applies to all information previously obtained by Dizzywood. Dizzywood reserves the right to change its privacy policy at its sole discretion. Dizzywood users will be informed of any such change by Dizzywood posting a new privacy policy on the Dizzywood Site. The effective date of any change of the privacy policy will be clearly marked. 

Dizzywood is committed to providing a fun, entertaining, and safe website for people of all ages. Our information practices are designed to comply with the United States Federal Trade Commission’s Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act “COPPA”. This Privacy Policy is part of our Terms of Use for the Site. Please review this Privacy Policy regularly so that you will be aware of any changes to it. Your continued use of the Site and/or provision of personally identifiable information by you to us following any such revision means you accept and will be subject to the revised Privacy Policy. Any revision to our data collection, use and disclosure practices that might require notice and/or verifiable parental consent for users of our Site under the age of 13 will be done in accordance with COPPA. Any terms not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meanings given such terms in the Terms of Use.  
Privo’s Privacy Assurance Program 

Dizzywood (www.dizzywood.com) is a participant in the Privo’s Privacy Assurance Program. As part of participating in the Privacy Assurance Program, Dizzywood adheres to the strict information collection, use and disclosure requirements. Privo is an independent, third party organization committed to safeguarding children’s personal information collected online, and to helping parents and their children exercise control over personal information while exploring the Internet. The seal posted on this page indicates that Dizzywood has established privacy practices and has agreed to submit to Privo’s oversight and consumer dispute resolution process. If you have questions or concerns about our privacy practices, please contact us at (800) 387-6907 or privacy@dizzywood.com. If you have further concerns after you have contacted Dizzywood, you can contact Privo directly at privacy@privo.com.  
Personal Information Collection and Use Policies 

It is our policy to require only the minimal collection of information from our users. We do not condition a child’s participation in any of our online activities on the disclosure of more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity. 

The safety of our users has always been our highest priority and to that end, we have devised a registration system that is intended to be completed by the parent on behalf of their child, unless the player is over 13 years of age. Parental permission is not required of players who are older than 13. 

In the registration process to become a member of Dizzywood, we ask the parent or player to click on links stating that they have read both the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use and that they agree to comply with both. We then ask the player, or a parent to choose for their child, a username (not a personally identifiable name) and password and to provide the player’s gender. We ask for username and password so that each time a player logs on they have their saved, personalized avatar and collected points available to them for play in Dizzywood. We ask for gender in order to program the player’s avatar as a boy or girl character. We ask for the birthdate of the player, so we can verify if parental permission is needed. 

Finally, for children under 13, we ask for a parent email so that we can send an email to the parent which directs them to click on a link in the email to activate the child’s account to chat on the Site. We prevent children from revealing personal information online and maintain an extremely safe environment with an advanced technology platform and live, trained moderators. 

We may also collect additional types of information from parents or guardians (such as credit card and billing information) when purchasing a subscription to the Site. A billing address collected during the purchase of a subscription may be used to send welcome information and other marketing materials. We use a third party vendor to process the data and they are contractually required to protect the privacy and security of the data. We do not store any of the credit card information in our database. 

The email addresses we collect are primarily used for our automated account activation and password retrieval systems and to verify parental consent of children to use the Site. We retain the right to communicate safety and privacy messages, general updates, and usability features via email. For special reasons, we may also send marketing materials such as special offers, coupons, and promotions for Dizzywood players. Parents can unsubscribe from these messages at any time by following the “unsubscribe” instructions found in the emails. 

In addition, we offer parents the option to sign up for a Dizzywood newsletter. When signing up for the newsletter, we ask for a parent’s email address that is used to confirm the request and to send newsletter updates on a regular basis. We will also provide an “unsubscribe” link in the newsletter emails. 

If an account has been inactive for 12 months or longer, we reserve the right to purge all of the user information associated with the account from our database. 

#### Parental Review of Information

Parents, please send a letter or postcard to our Privacy Manager at the mailing address provided below if you would like to do any of the following: 

Access the personally identifiable information that Dizzywood has collected online about your child, correct factual errors in such information, request to have this information deleted, or request that we no longer collect or maintain such information. Please note that this may require that we cancel and delete your child’s account. 

Please be sure to include your email address and a telephone number where we can reach you. To protect your child’s privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting you access to the information that we collect and maintain about your child. 

#### Communication Tools

Dizzywood’s communication tools facilitate interactivity within our community. These tools include real-time chat. Dizzywood chat is protected by our proprietary filter technology, selective monitoring by staff members, and peer reporting to prevent users from sharing personal information. 

In the future, Dizzywood may offer its members additional community services such as the ability to post messages in forums, or upload other content such as artwork, images and videos to Dizzywood. These submissions will go through an approval process that requires pre-moderation before the post goes live up on Dizzywood, until a user proves to be a responsible community member. Thereafter, their messages will be filtered and post-moderated. Parents who have given their consent for their child’s contributions to post immediately without prior review by Dizzywood staff will be contacted when these tools become available, at which time they can choose to opt-out of this member benefit. 

#### Cookies

Dizzywood uses a software technology called “cookies.” Cookies are small text files that we place in visitors’ computer browsers to store their preferences. Cookies themselves do not contain any personally identifiable information. Although cookies could enable us to relate a visitor’s use of this website to personal information that a visitor has provided, such as an email address, we do not use them for this purpose. We do use “cookies” to determine how many visitors we have and how often they visit various sections of our Site. 

#### Web Visit Logs

We may collect information about you through technology we use to make our website more interesting and useful to you. We routinely collect our users’ visit information including pages visited on Dizzywood, the date and time of the visit, IP address, and the version of browser used. We use this information for improving Dizzywood’s content and services and for investigating cases of suspected abuse. 

#### Third Parties

We do not share any personally identifiable information of our users with any third parties, commercial or otherwise, except that we may provide such information to parties involved in a merger, consolidation or other reorganization of Dizzywood or to a party that purchases substantially all of our assets related to the Site. We may, however, also comply with requests for personally identifiable information from law enforcement or other governmental agencies, or requested pursuant to subpoena. We may share aggregated statistical data with our sponsors, partners, or the general public. 

This privacy policy applies only to information collected on this site. The site may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Dizzywood. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy policies of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the site and to read the privacy policies of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information. 

#### Your California Privacy Rights

Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our users who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of our users’ personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email or write us: 

Rocket Paper Scissors LLC  
ATTN: Privacy Coordinator  
720 Market Street, 4th Floor  
San Francisco, CA 94102  
(800) 387-6907  
privacy@dizzywood.com

#### Contact Information

Dizzywood.com is owned, produced, operated and maintained by Rocket Paper Scissors, LLC. For questions regarding Dizzywood, please email privacy@dizzywood.com. Please note that this email address is used only to respond to inquiries related to user privacy. All other emails sent to this account will be deleted. 

Rocket Paper Scissors LLC  
ATTN: Privacy Coordinator  
720 Market Street, 4th Floor  
San Francisco, CA 94102  
(800) 387-6907  
privacy@dizzywood.com
